Aleksandr Krivonosov

Objective: C++ software developer

Primary Skills:

- C++
- Java
- JavaScript
- SQL
- R
- C#

Professional Highlights

Information Technology professional in software development including servers, multithreading programs, network games, add-ins for CAD systems. Also have experience in 3D graphics, driver development, construction of mathematical models of complex systems, creating simple sites, predicting data using neural networks. Able to design multithreaded processes and make joint and independent decisions.

Work experience

WILDECC++ Developer

06/2016 - 02/2018

AMCbridge 02/2018 05/2019

C++ Developer 03/2018 - 05/2019

Education

DNU named after Oles' Honchar

2013 - 2018

Master's degree in Applied Mathematics, educational program: computer modeling and computational methods.

Personal features and information

English level: upper-intermediate.

Contacts:

email: sahlet.official@gmail.com

skype: sahlet